Harold Weston Papers
Harold Weston Papers
- Correspondence subject files
  - Stokes, Emlen and Lydia, 1942-1943 (Box 23)
  - Stone, Edward D., 1959-1960 (Box 23)
  - Swados, Harvey, 1960 (Box 23)
  - Swing, Richard, 1947 (Box 23)
  - Taft, Robert A., Jr., 1960; 1964 (Box 23)
  - Taylor, Billy, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Taylor, Dean P., 1947; 1951,; 1956 (Box 23)
  - Thompson, Frank, Jr., 1955-1965 (Box 24)
  - Thornberry, Homer, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Tillich, Paul, 1963 (Box 24)
  - Tolley, William P., 1967 (Box 24)
  - Treadwell, Helen, 1958 (Box 24)
  - Trilling, Lionel, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Trimble, James W., 1956 (Box 24)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1945-1947 (Box 24)
  - Udall, Stewart, 1961 (Box 24)
  - United Nations, undated (Box 24)
  - United Nations Economic and Social Council, 1950 (Box 24)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1950-1965 (Box 24)
  - United Nations Food and Agriculture Organization, 1950 (Box 24)
  - United Nations International Children’s Emergency Fund (UNICEF), 1947 (Box 24)
  - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRRA), 1945-1947 (Box 24)
  - United Nations World Health Organization (WHO), 1950 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1947; 1957 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1955-1962 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of State, 1961-1964 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of the Interior, 1961 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of the Treasury, 1965 (Box 24)
  - United States Information Agency, 1956-1968 (Box 25)
  - United States Post Office Department, 1963-1964 (Box 25)
  - Wagner, Robert F., 1955-1965 (Box 25)
  - Wainwright, Stuyvesant Walker, Ralph, 1958; 1962 (Box 25)
  - Welles, Sumner, 1945 (Box 25)
  - Weston, Faith, 1945 (Box 25)
  - Whitaker, Frederick, 1955 (Box 25)
  - Widnall, William, 1963 (Box 25)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Williams, Harrison, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Williams, John J., 1960 (Box 25)
  - Wiley, Alexander, 1947 (Box 25)
  - Wood, Peggy, 1960-1965 (Box 25)
  - Wooley, Mary E., 1942-1947 (Box 25)
  - Wyckoff, Florence, 1946-1947 (Box 25)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Yarborough, Ralph, 1965 (Box 25)
  - Yates, Sidney, 1959 (Box 25)
  - Zeidler, Frank P., 1958 (Box 25)
- Memorabilia
  - Clippings
    - Miscellaneous, 1920-1957; 5 folders (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958-1965; undated (Box 26)
  - Exhibitions
    - Announcements and invitations, 1935-1963 (Box 26)
    - Catalogs, 1937-1964 (Box 26)
  - Photographs
    - Adirondacks, 220 negatives (Box 29)
    - Ashur (Qal’at Sherqat), undated; 18 negatives (Box 29)
    - Babylon, undated; 8 negatives (Box 29)
    - Baghdad City YMCA, Kadg Main, undated; 35 negatives (Box 29)
    - Baghdad YMCA, advanced base, undated; 28 negatives (Box 29)
    - Baku, Persia, undated; 6 negatives (Box 29)
    - Baquba [Iraq], Assyrian refugees, undated; 25 negatives (Box 29)
    - Bisotun, Kangavar, Motor convoy to Hamedan, undated; 20 negatives (Box 29)
    - British military, Mesopotamia, undated; 30 negatives (Box 29)
    - Building (cottage studies), 1920; 18 negatives (Box 29)
    - Buria, undated; 16 negatives (Box 29)
    - Caravan, undated; 10 negatives (Box 29)
    - Ceylon, Singapore, undated; 13 negatives (Box 29)
    - China – Hong Kong, Canton, undated; 20 negatives (Box 29)
    - China – Peking – Summer Palace, Forbidden City, undated; 18 negatives (Box 29)
    - China – Shanghai, Peking City, undated; 24 negatives (Box 29)
    - Coming up the Tigris, undated; 10 negatives (Box 29)
    - Delbid, undated; 16 negatives (Box 29)
    - Elburz Mountains, undated; 12 negatives (Box 29)
    - Exeter, undated; 5 negatives (Box 29)
    - Food for Freedom, undated; 5 prints (Box 26)
    - Gardens, Palms, undated; 9 negatives (Box 29)
    - Hamadan, 1919; 12 negatives (Box 29)
    - Hamadan City – people, missions, 1918; 18 negatives (Box 29)
    - Hamadan environs, Alvand Range, undated; 21 negatives (Box 29)
    - Honolulu, undated; 8 negatives (Box 29)
    - India, Baghdad, 1916; 19 negatives (Box 29)
    - India – Jutagh, Linda, 1916; 30 negatives (Box 29)
    - India – Madras, Madura, 1919; 41 negatives (Box 29)
    - India – Poona, Delhi, undated; 14 negatives (Box 29)
    - Isfahan, undated; 42 negatives (Box 29)
    - International Association of the Plastic Arts, undated; 9 prints (Box 26)
    - Japan – Kyoto, Tokyo, Kanakura, undated; 22 negatives (Box 29)
    - Japan – Nikkor, undated; 14 negatives (Box 29)
    - Karind, undated; negatives (Box 29)
    - Karmanshah, Motor convoy, 1918; 27 negatives (Box 29)
    - Kashan to Isfahan, undated; 3 negatives (Box 29)
    - Kazvin, undated; 12 negatives (Box 29)
    - Kermanshah, undated; 17 negatives (Box 29)
    - Khanikin, undated; 11 negatives (Box 29)
    - Korea, undated; 12 negatives (Box 29)
    - Lower Lake, 1920; negatives (Box 29)
    - Marion, 1911-1912; 3 negatives (Box 29)
    - Marseilles – “La Tourraine”, 1916; 9 negatives (Box 29)
    - Nantucket, 1912; 6 negatives (Box 29)
    - Naqsh-e-Rustam, undated; 11 negatives
    - Nomad tents, undated; 4 negatives (Box 29)
    - Pasargadae, undated; 10 negatives (Box 29)
    - People, 1920; 11 negatives (Box 29)
    - Persepolis, undated; 26 negatives (Box 29)
    - Persia – Irrigation, ploughing, undated; negatives (Box 29)
    - Persian characters – men and women, undated; 14 negatives (Box 29)
    - Qasr-e Shirin, undated; 12 negatives (Box 29)
    - Quizal Rolat, undated; 5 negatives (Box 29)
    - Reslat, undated; 4 negatives (Box 29)
    - Rugs, undated; 7 negatives (Box 29)
    - Sarnak, undated; 9 negatives (Box 29)
    - Sheikland, undated; 10 negatives (Box 29)
    - Shiraz, undated; 22 negatives (Box 29)
    - Snow, 1920; 20 negatives (Box 29)
    - Spring Street, 1920; 8 negatives (Box 29)
    - Table Mountain, Sindigah, Military pontoon bridge over Diahla River, undated; 8 negatives (Box 29)
    - Takht-i-Bostan, undated; 8 negatives (Box 29)
    - Teheran, undated; 10 negatives (Box 29)
    - Tigris River- Mahelas, Marsh Arabs, undated; 19 negatives (Box 29)
    - Trotsky, Leon with Natalia Sedova and Harold and Faith Weston, Mexico, 1936; 3 prints (Box 26)
    - Upper Lake, 1920; 11 negatives (Box 29)
    - Weston, Harold, 1952; 1960,; 1969; 5 prints (Box 26)
    - Yezdikbast, undated; 15 negatives (Box 29)
    - YMCA, undated; 23 negatives (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous untitled, undated; 149 prints (Box 29)
- Writings
  - Articles
    - Adventures in the gardens of the Persian potentates, undated (Box 27)
    - Being a woman in Persia, undated (Box 27)
    - A modern Sennacherib, undated (Box 27)
    - A painter speaks, undated (Box 27)
    - Red letter day, undated (Box 27)
    - Sate support- a rebuttal, undated (Box 27)
    - Who pays the piper?, undated (Box 27)
  - Books
    - Battle of bread
      - Early draft entirely revised - partial, undated (Box 27)
      - Draft A chapters 1-4, undated (Box 27)
      - Draft A chapters 5-12, undated (Box 27)
      - Draft A appendix, undated (Box 27)
      - Draft B chapters 1-5, undated (Box 27)
      - Draft B chapters 6-12, undated (Box 27)
      - Draft C chapters 3-10, undated (Box 27)
      - Miscellaneous drafts and revisions, undated (Box 27)
  - Speeches
    - Arts and government – written for Sen. Herbert Lehman, 1956 (Box 28)
    - The arts, the community and government, 1962 (Box 28)
    - The arts in the United States-yesterday, today and tomorrow, 1961 (Box 28)
    - The arts in the United States – the second half of the Twentieth Century, 1963 (Box 28)
    - Coming to grips about UNRRA, 1945 (Box 28)
    - Federal and state legislation for the arts, 1961 (Box 28)
    - Federal subsidies for the arts, 1962 (Box 28)
    - Food and the peace, undated (Box 28)
    - Food-builder of peace, 1945 (Box 28)
    - Government should help to advance the arts in the United States, 1961 (Box 28)
    - The government’s role in multiple responsibility for the arts, 1962 (Box 28)
    - The inside story of the Hoover Report, 1946 (Box 28)
    - To the limits of our strength, 1946 (Box 28)
    - Positive aspects of governmental support of the arts, 1963 (Box 28)
    - Public responsibility of the arts, 1961 (Box 28)
    - The proposed Federal Advisory Council on the Arts., 1961 (Box 28)
    - Remarks after receiving the American Society of Contemporary Artists’ award, 1964 (Box 28)
    - The Role of the artist in national life, 1964 (Box 28)
    - The role of the government in the arts in the United States., 1961 (Box 28)
    - United Nations relief, 1944 (Box 28)
    - The voice of the American artist, 1958 (Box 28)
    - What the citizen wants to know about UNRRA, 1944 (Box 28)